<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest news </title>
    <link>http://hemantmandi.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Latest news </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://hemantmandi.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Aadhaar Card: How to Verify Your Phone Number.</title>
      <link>http://hemantmandi.github.io/how-to-verify-phone-number-email-address-aadhaarcard/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://hemantmandi.github.io/how-to-verify-phone-number-email-address-aadhaarcard/</guid>
      <description>Are you sure that the contact information registered with Unique Identification Authority of India (UIDAI) for your Aadhaar Card is correct? If not, we would advise you to head to the UIDAI website and check it out for yourself. Aadhaar card is increasingly becoming the most important proof of identification and considering that the government has made it mandatory to link your Aadhaar cards with PAN card for filing income tax returns, its importance has grown further.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bank of Baroda Follows SBI, Cuts Interest On Savings Accounts</title>
      <link>http://hemantmandi.github.io/bank-of-baroda-follows-sbi-cuts-interest-on-savings-accounts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://hemantmandi.github.io/bank-of-baroda-follows-sbi-cuts-interest-on-savings-accounts/</guid>
      <description>Within days of SBI slashing interest rate on savings bank account, another PSU bank &amp;ndash; Bank of Baroda &amp;ndash; has followed suit, cutting it to 3.5 per cent on deposits of up to Rs 50 lakh.
&amp;ldquo;We wish to inform you that it has been decided to introduce a 2-tier savings bank interest rate (from) August 5&amp;hellip;,&amp;rdquo; the bank said in a regulatory filing. Effective tomorrow, the interest rate on savings bank balance of up to Rs 50 lakh has been reduced to 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Banks Rush To Buy Cyber Security Cover As Digi Payments Rise</title>
      <link>http://hemantmandi.github.io/banks-rush-to-buy-cyber-security-cover-as-digi-payments-rise/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://hemantmandi.github.io/banks-rush-to-buy-cyber-security-cover-as-digi-payments-rise/</guid>
      <description>The government may cut back some of the plethora of socio-economic schemes that have outlived their utility as it uses outcome budgeting to assess the impact of central sector schemes, a top official said.
In a bid to improve quality of public expenditure, the finance ministry has asked every ministry to prepare outcome budget statement linking outlays against each scheme with deliverables achieved and their impact on economy and citizens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Banks on Strike 22 August</title>
      <link>http://hemantmandi.github.io/bank-strike-on-august-22-to-protest-against-proposed-reforms/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://hemantmandi.github.io/bank-strike-on-august-22-to-protest-against-proposed-reforms/</guid>
      <description>United Forum of Banking Unions (UFBU), the umbrella body of trade unions in the banking sector, has called a nation-wide strike on August 22 to protest against the reforms proposed by the Centre.
West Bengal convenor of UFBU, Siddhartha Khan said that the government is ushering in privatisation and consolidation in the Indian banking sector in the garb of reforms.
He said that the Bank Board Bureau had been formed to bring all the public sector banks (PSBs) under a banking investment company and get the government&amp;rsquo;s share in PSBs below 50 per cent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EPFO To Launch Online PF Withdrawal Facility Soon: 10 Things To Know</title>
      <link>http://hemantmandi.github.io/epfo-to-launch-online-pf-withdrawal-facility-soon-10-things-to-know/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://hemantmandi.github.io/epfo-to-launch-online-pf-withdrawal-facility-soon-10-things-to-know/</guid>
      <description>The launch of this facility will not only ease the process for subscribers but also speed up the processing time.
The Employees&amp;rsquo; Provident Fund Organisation or EPFO is expected to soon launch an online facility for withdrawal of provident fund (PF) money and pension fixation. The launch of this facility will not only ease the process for subscribers but also speed up the processing time. &amp;ldquo;The process of connecting all field offices with a central server is going on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Government Issuing New-Look And Tamper-Proof PAN Cards</title>
      <link>http://hemantmandi.github.io/government-issuing-new-look-and-tamper-proof-pan-cards/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://hemantmandi.github.io/government-issuing-new-look-and-tamper-proof-pan-cards/</guid>
      <description>The Government is issuing newly designed PAN (Permanent Account Number) cards that have added security features to make them tamper-proof and with contents written in both Hindi and English, a senior Income-Tax Department official said today.
The distribution of new-look PAN cards, being printed by NSDL and UTIITSL (UTI Infrastructure Technology and Services Ltd), started since January 1. The cards are being issued to new applicants but existing ones can only apply for them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Government Slash Prices Of Knee Implants. Details Here</title>
      <link>http://hemantmandi.github.io/government-caps-prices-of-knee-implants-details-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://hemantmandi.github.io/government-caps-prices-of-knee-implants-details-here/</guid>
      <description>Drug pricing regulator NPPA (National Pharmaceutical Pricing Authority) on Wednesday announced a price cap on knee replacements. NPPA, which had earlier put limits on the prices of coronary stents, slashed the prices of total knee replacement systems and their individual components by as much as 69 per cent, an official notification issued by NPPA said. According to the price ceiling notice, the price of total knee implants made of cobalt chromium has now been capped at Rs 54,720, down 65 per cent from its average maximum retail price of Rs 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indian Army will get Apache attack choppers</title>
      <link>http://hemantmandi.github.io/government-approves-procuring-six-apache-attack-choppers-for-indian-army/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://hemantmandi.github.io/government-approves-procuring-six-apache-attack-choppers-for-indian-army/</guid>
      <description>In a major decision, the defence ministry approved procurement of six Apache helicopters along with weapons systems from American giant Boeing at a cost of Rs 4,168 crore for the Army which will be its first fleet of attack choppers. It will be a follow on order to the deal India had signed with Boeing and the US government for 22 Apache helicopters and 15 Chinook heavy-lift choppers in September 2015.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jio Phone Offline Bookings Begin: Delivery Date, Documents You Need, Price, and More Details</title>
      <link>http://hemantmandi.github.io/jio-phone-bookings-offline-pre-order-registration-delivery-date-price-aadhaar-card-document/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://hemantmandi.github.io/jio-phone-bookings-offline-pre-order-registration-delivery-date-price-aadhaar-card-document/</guid>
      <description>Jio Phone bookings have opened in certain offline retail stores in the Delhi-NCR area, ahead of the scheduled August 24 date that was announced at the Reliance AGM on July 21. If you have such an offline retailer taking Jio Phone bookings right now, you can be ahead of the millions who are expected to buy the handset when bookings officially open. Gadgets 360 spoke to one such retailer to find out the details of the pre-order process, the documents needed, how many units a person can order, delivery date, and when the Rs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PAN Migration: Do You Need It? And How To Do It</title>
      <link>http://hemantmandi.github.io/pan-migration-do-you-need-it-and-how-to-do-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://hemantmandi.github.io/pan-migration-do-you-need-it-and-how-to-do-it/</guid>
      <description>PAN or Permanent Account Number is issued by the Income Tax department with details including date of birth, name and PAN number of the individual. A PAN number allotted to a person is a 10-digit alphanumeric number used in to link all of his or her financial transactions with the unique ID such as tax payments, income tax return and wealth tax return. PAN, thus, acts as a financial identifier for the person with the tax department.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vodafone Offers Unlimited Voice Calling, 1GB Data Per Day at Rs. 348</title>
      <link>http://hemantmandi.github.io/vodafone-348-prepaid-recharge-offer-rajasthan-unlimited-voice-calling/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://hemantmandi.github.io/vodafone-348-prepaid-recharge-offer-rajasthan-unlimited-voice-calling/</guid>
      <description>HIGHLIGHTS
 Vodafone&amp;rsquo;s new prepaid plan offers unlimited voice calling It is priced at Rs. 348 and offers 1GB per day of data benefits The recharge plan is available for Rajasthan subscribers only  In a bid to combat the Reliance Jio competition, Vodafone has now launched a special recharge plan for prepaid users in Rajasthan. The Vodafone 348 Prepaid Recharge offer comes with unlimited voice calling benefits and 1GB of 4G data per day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your PAN card could be invalid without Aadhaar by December. Here’s what to do</title>
      <link>http://hemantmandi.github.io/your-pan-card-could-be-invalid-without-aadhaar-by-december/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://hemantmandi.github.io/your-pan-card-could-be-invalid-without-aadhaar-by-december/</guid>
      <description>Permanent account numbers (PAN) not linked to Aadhaar cards will likely become invalid after December 31, a government source said on Thursday, as the Centre pushes to widen the use of the 12-digit biometric identity project.
Permanent account numbers (PAN) not linked to Aadhaar cards will likely become invalid after December 31, a government source said on Thursday, as the Centre pushes to widen the use of the 12-digit biometric identity project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>e-facility to link Aadhaar with PAN launched</title>
      <link>http://hemantmandi.github.io/e-facility-link-aadhaar-pan-launched/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://hemantmandi.github.io/e-facility-link-aadhaar-pan-launched/</guid>
      <description>I-T Department asks people to ensure that the date of birth and gender in PAN and Aadhaar are exactly the same, to ensure linkage without failure.
The Income Tax Department has launched an e-facility to link Aadhaar with Permanent Account Number (PAN), a mandatory procedure for filing IT returns now.
The department’s e-filing website https://incometaxindiaefiling.gov.in has created the link on its homepage.
The link requires the PAN, the Aadhaar number and the “exact name as given in the Aadhaar card”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>your Aadhaar is safe</title>
      <link>http://hemantmandi.github.io/dont-panic-aadhaar-safe-writes-rs-sharma/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://hemantmandi.github.io/dont-panic-aadhaar-safe-writes-rs-sharma/</guid>
      <description>Amidst concerns regarding Aadhaar data leak, a look at how the unique identification system actually adheres to the principles of privacy
Privacy and data protection concerns have become serious in a digital world due to ease of search and aggregation, with or without Aadhaar. Type any name in Google and it will throw up thousands of results, giving data/information publicly available. Hence, the responsibility falls on organisations which collect data from individuals to protect it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>आधार कार्ड से नहीं जोड़ने पर अवैध हो जाएगा PAN,</title>
      <link>http://hemantmandi.github.io/your-pan-card-could-be-invalid-without-aadhaar/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://hemantmandi.github.io/your-pan-card-could-be-invalid-without-aadhaar/</guid>
      <description>अगर आपने परमानेंट अकाउंट नंबर (PAN) को आधार कार्ड से नहीं जोड़ा तो संभव है कि 31 दिसंबर के बाद यह अवैध हो जाए। दरअसल, इनकम टैक्स रिटर्न और PAN के लिए आधार को अनिवार्य बनाने के सरकार के फैसले के बाद इसे वित्तीय लेनदेन (फाइनैंशल ट्रांजैक्शंज) के लिए जरूरी नंबर बनाने की दिशा में एक और कदम बढ़ा दिया गया है। सरकार पूरे फाइनैंशल सेक्टर में आधार आधारित नो योर कस्टमर (KYC) को इंटीग्रेट करने पर विचार कर रही है।</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>पेट्रोल-डीजल प्राइस रोज बदलने से किसका लाभ?</title>
      <link>http://hemantmandi.github.io/daily-fuel-price-revisions-to-boost/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://hemantmandi.github.io/daily-fuel-price-revisions-to-boost/</guid>
      <description>पेट्रोल-डीजल के खुदरा मूल्यों का रोजाना संशोधन करने के सरकार के फैसले से तेल कंपनियों के मार्जिन में सुधार आएगा और उन्हें अच्छा मुनाफा होने की संभावना है। इंडिया रेटिंग ने सोमवार को अपनी रिपोर्ट में कहा कि सरकार के इस कदम की सराहना किया। रिपोर्ट में कहा गया है कि 2010 में पेट्रोल के दाम को, 2014 में डीजल के दाम को नियंत्रण मुक्त करने, एलपीजी से संबंधित गिव इट अप योजना, पीडीएस केरोसिन आवंटन घटाने और उसके दामों में क्रमिक वृद्धि के बाद मार्केटिंग सेक्टर में यह एक अन्य सकारात्मक ढांचागत बदलाव है।</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>