<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Digital Payment on Latest news </title>
    <link>http://hemantmandi.github.io/tags/digital-payment/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Digital Payment on Latest news </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://hemantmandi.github.io/tags/digital-payment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Bank of Baroda Follows SBI, Cuts Interest On Savings Accounts</title>
      <link>http://hemantmandi.github.io/bank-of-baroda-follows-sbi-cuts-interest-on-savings-accounts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://hemantmandi.github.io/bank-of-baroda-follows-sbi-cuts-interest-on-savings-accounts/</guid>
      <description>Within days of SBI slashing interest rate on savings bank account, another PSU bank &amp;ndash; Bank of Baroda &amp;ndash; has followed suit, cutting it to 3.5 per cent on deposits of up to Rs 50 lakh.
&amp;ldquo;We wish to inform you that it has been decided to introduce a 2-tier savings bank interest rate (from) August 5&amp;hellip;,&amp;rdquo; the bank said in a regulatory filing. Effective tomorrow, the interest rate on savings bank balance of up to Rs 50 lakh has been reduced to 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>e-facility to link Aadhaar with PAN launched</title>
      <link>http://hemantmandi.github.io/e-facility-link-aadhaar-pan-launched/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://hemantmandi.github.io/e-facility-link-aadhaar-pan-launched/</guid>
      <description>I-T Department asks people to ensure that the date of birth and gender in PAN and Aadhaar are exactly the same, to ensure linkage without failure.
The Income Tax Department has launched an e-facility to link Aadhaar with Permanent Account Number (PAN), a mandatory procedure for filing IT returns now.
The department’s e-filing website https://incometaxindiaefiling.gov.in has created the link on its homepage.
The link requires the PAN, the Aadhaar number and the “exact name as given in the Aadhaar card”.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>